NICOLE FLOYD

SKILLS

Programming: HTML5, Javascript, CSS3, PHP, SQL, Python, Bootstrap, React, NodeJS

Additional: Agile Methodologies, EDI, Database Management, Change Management, SharePoint, Remote Access/End User Support, Quality Management

EXPERIENCE

Project Manager | RBW Logistics | 2006 – 2018

- Developed and maintained Warehouse Mangement Systems.
- Developed software end-user guides and procedures.
- Provided advanced-level IT support.
- Created and managed ISO quality program.
- Maintained a 95% or higher Quality Audit Record for seven plus years.
- Developed safety campaigns, safety systems, policies and procedures.
- Trained management and associates on software, quality and safety policies and procedures.

Administrative Assistant | CCAP,Inc | 2004 – 2006

- Planned and coordinated logistics and materials for executive board meetings and staff events.
- Drafted flyers, brochures and public service announcements to promote programs.
- Procured donations for non-profit, religious organizations and individuals.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Development | 2018 | Augusta Innovation Academy

Lead Auditor | 2015 | Georgia Tech Innovation Institute

Internal Auditor | 2011 | Georgia Tech Innovation Institute

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with over ten years of project management experience. Knowledgeable in programming languages, design, development and testing software. Broad experience in warehousing and logistics, client relations, training and development.





ni.floyd@icloud.com

706.627.6445





www.linkedin.com/i n/NiFloyd

github.com/NiFloyd

Website:

www.nicolebrands.com

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Website Administrator

2017-2018

Local Non-Profit Organization

Event Manager

2014-2017

Women's Conference for New Zion Hill

NICOLE FLOYD



ni.floyd@icloud.com



www.linkedin.com/in/NiFloyd



706.627.6445



github.com/NiFloyd

REFERENCES

Matt Hill, Senior Developer & Software Development Instructor
Greater Augusta Innovation Academy
540 Telfair St, Augusta, GA 30901
706.723.5782
matt@theclubhou.se

Rebecca Wells, Executive Assistant Augusta Warrior Project 701 Greene St, Augusta, GA 30901 706.313.3591 beckywells8@hotmail.com

Rev. Millicent West, Executive Assistant New Zion Hill Missionary Baptist Church 3237 ½ Deans Bridge Road, Augusta, GA 30901 706.793.8512 ladymwest@comcast.net

Timothy Brittingham, Trade Compliance
XPO Logistics
6701 Old Statesville Rd, Charlotte, NC 28269
803.226.6423
Tim.britt1966@yahoo.com